Contact

2515814321 (Mobile) blakerobertyoung@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/blakeyoung-55665b75 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Interventional Radiology Electrophysiology **ACLS**

Blake Young

Interventional Radiology/Cardiac Cath Lab

San Francisco Bay Area

Summary

Extensive experience in all fields of cardiac (diagnostic/ interventional), vascular, electrophysiology and interventional radiology, and Neuro Interventional studies. ACLS / BLS / PALS certified. Stroke certified. Easily adaptable in any health care arena. Posses remarkable intrapersonal and communication skills across a multi-faceted practice. Skilled with Epic, Witt, Xper, Sunrise, and Maclabs software.

Experience

University of California, San Francisco RN - Interventional Radiology / Neuro August 2014 - Present (6 years)

San Francisco, California

Washington Hospital Healthcare System Travel RN - Coronary Angiography \ Interventional Radiology April 2014 - July 2014 (4 months)

fremont, california

Stanford Hospital & Clinics

Travel RN- Coronary Angiography / interventional Radiology June 2013 - April 2014 (11 months)

palo alto, california

CORONARY ANGIOGRAPHY- left heart catheterization, right heart catheterization, root angiography, PTCA, cutting balloon, rotoblator, coronary pressure (FFR/CFR), thrombectomy, pericardiocentesis, LVAD, IABP, PFO closure, ASD/VSD closure, TAVR

PERIPHERAL ANGIOGRAPHY- bilateral extremity angiography, abdominal angiography, renal angiography, carotid angiography, venography, PTA, IVC placement

DEVICE IMPLANTS- single/dual chamber PPM/ICD, bi-ventricular implants, generator exchange, lead revision, pocket revision

INTERVENTIONAL RADIOLOGY- TIPSS, portal vein stents, PICC/CVC placement, IVC filter (insertion & removal), chemo embolization (SIR spheres & Theraspheres), endovascular aneurysm repair, percutaneous gastrostomy & jejunostomy placement, nephrostogram, ureteral stent placement, paracentesis, abscess drainage, chest tube placement, cholangiogram, biliary drain placement, cholecystostomy, transjugular liver biopsy

St. Luke's Episcopal Hospital Travel RN- Coronary Angiography February 2013 - May 2013 (4 months) Houston, Texas

CORONARY ANGIOGRAPHY- left heart catheterization, right heart catheterization, root angiography, PTCA, cutting balloon, rotoblator, coronary pressure (FFR/CFR), thrombectomy, pericardiocentesis, LVAD, IABP, PFO closure, ASD/VSD closure, TAVR

PERIPHERAL ANGIOGRAPHY- bilateral extremity angiography, abdominal angiography, renal angiography, carotid angiography, venography, PTA, IVC placement

ELECTROPHYSIOLOGY- atrial ablations, ventricular ablations
DEVICE IMPLANTS- single/dual chamber PPM/ICD, bi-ventricular implants,
generator exchange, lead revision, pocket revision

Mobile Infirmary Medical Center
RN Coronary / Vascular Angiography
December 2011 - February 2013 (1 year 3 months)

Diagnostic & Interventional Coronary Angiography / Peripheral Angiography / Endovascular / ICD & Pacemaker Device Implants

IHS Diagnostic & Medical Clini
RN Cardiac Manager
September 2010 - December 2011 (1 year 4 months)
mobile, alabama

Supervised and coordinated all diagnostic cardiac testing for high volume outpatient facility. Nuclear Imaging / Stress Sonography/ Telemetry Monitoring/ Electrocardiograph

Education

University of Mobile BSN, Nursing (2008 - 2010)

Auburn University

Liberal Arts and Sciences/Liberal Studies · (2003 - 2005)